PA, Pittsburgh katelynk44@gmail.com (724) 622-6289

# KATELYN KUNZMANN

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

US Citizen

### PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Collaborative and detail-focused Software Engineer with experience in developing and deploying secure applications. Skilled in various programming languages including C#, Java, and Python. Strong communication and teamwork skills with a passion for continuous learning and growth in the field of software engineering.

#### **EMPLOYMENT HISTORY**

NOV 2023 - PRESENT

#### Software Engineer Associate, UPMC, Pittsburgh, PA

- Maintained and developed critical features for entire claims and billing system ensuring compliance with HIPAA and industry standards
- · Provided effective support for production issues, identifying root causes and implementing corrective actions
- Improved technical documentation

JUN 2023 - AUG 2023

## Software Engineer Intern, Tackle.io, Remote

- Designed, developed and deployed a reverse proxy server that securely stores AWS credentials and facilitates API calls with AWS services
- · Set up PostgreSQL database that securely holds 500 AWS account credentials
- · Containerized application into a Linux Docker container

JAN 2023 - MAR 2023

#### Malware Analyst Intern, National Cyber-Forensics and Training Alliance (NCFTA), Pittsburgh, PA

- Developed a new malware analysis tool
- Conducted static and dynamic analysis on malware and ransomware variants
- Wrote technical reports on malware variants that were delivered to 100's of companies and law enforcement agencies around the world

## **EDUCATION**

AUG 2020 - AUG 2023

#### B.S. in Computer Science, University of Pittsburgh, Pittsburgh, PA

Relevant courses

- Data Structures & Algorithms I and II
- Operating Systems
- Applied Cryptography and Network Security
- · Cryptocurrencies, Blockchains, and Applications elective taken at Carnegie Mellon University

## **SKILLS**

Programming Languages: Java, Python, C, C#, .NET, SQL, Cloud: AWS

JavaScript, HTML, CSS, x86

Frameworks: React, FastAPI, HTTPX, Node.js, three.js, Databases: SQL Server, SSMS, PostgreSQL

Source Control: GitHub, Bitbucket Testing: Unit Testing, Selenium, Postman

Other Skills: Linux, Git

### LINKS

Portfolio Website Github

LinkedIn